export const words = [
  {
    name: "Gat",
    des: "For education",
    word: 12,
    score: "12/12",
    play: 92,
    date: "12/01/2565",
  },
  {
    name: "Eng commu",
    des: "For education",
    word: 20,
    score: "17/20",
    play: 845,
    date: "14/01/2565",
  },
  {
    name: "O-net",
    des: "For education",
    word: 55,
    score: "10/55",
    play: 2,
    date: "22/01/2565",
  },
  {
    name: "inturn",
    des: "For education",
    word: 0,
    score: "0/0",
    play: 0,
    date: "01/02/2565",
  },
  {
    name: "dev Eng",
    des: "For education",
    word: 100,
    score: "2/100",
    play: 25,
    date: "09/03/2565",
  },
];
export const datagame = [
  {
    question: "arrange",
    type: "Verb",
    answer: "จัดแจง",
    choice1: "กระดาน",
    choice2: "เมืองหลวง",
    choice3: "จัดแจง",
    choice4: "ช่างตัดผม",
  },
  {
    question: "barber",
    type: "Noun",
    answer: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice1: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice2: "จัดแจง",
    choice3: "เมืองหลวง",
    choice4: "ทวีป",
  },
  {
    question: "board",
    type: "Noun",
    answer: "กระดาน",
    choice1: "หนัก",
    choice2: "กระดาน",
    choice3: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice4: "จัดแจง",
  },
  {
    question: "capital",
    type: "Noun",
    answer: "เมืองหลวง",
    choice1: "จัดแจง",
    choice2: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice3: "ทวีป",
    choice4: "เมืองหลวง",
  },
  {
    question: "continent",
    type: "Noun",
    answer: "ทวีป",
    choice1: "โดยเฉพาะ",
    choice2: "กระดาน",
    choice3: "ทวีป",
    choice4: "หนัก",
  },
  {
    question: "crowd",
    type: "Noun",
    answer: "ฝูงชน",
    choice1: "กำหนด",
    choice2: "กระดาน",
    choice3: "ฝูงชน",
    choice4: "เมืองหลวง",
  },
  {
    question: "determine",
    type: "Verb",
    answer: "กำหนด",
    choice1: "กำหนด",
    choice2: "จัดแจง",
    choice3: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice4: "โดยเฉพาะ",
  },
  {
    question: "especially",
    type: "Adverb",
    answer: "โดยเฉพาะ",
    choice1: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice2: "โดยเฉพาะ",
    choice3: "เมืองหลวง",
    choice4: "จัดแจง",
  },
  {
    question: "forward",
    type: "Adjective",
    answer: "ซึ่งไปข้างหน้า",
    choice1: "เมืองหลวง",
    choice2: "ซึ่งไปข้างหน้า",
    choice3: "โดยเฉพาะ",
    choice4: "จัดแจง",
  },
  {
    question: "heavy",
    type: "Adjective",
    answer: "หนัก",
    choice1: "ช่างตัดผม",
    choice2: "จัดแจง",
    choice3: "ซึ่งไปข้างหน้า",
    choice4: "หนัก",
  },
]